{
    "id": "de99a7d9d5214025a407f5dd755bcd4c",
    "title": "Auxiliaries Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "b99bfb3fb1ac45ad8e95ee45c202e02d",
            "title": "Auxiliaries Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The boy …………………… playing the piano.",
                    "description": "We use is here because the subject is the singular countable noun boy.",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "are",
                        "has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We ………………………… sent the parcel.",
                    "description": "We use the present perfect to talk about recently finished actions or situations. This verb form is made with has or have.",
                    "answers": [
                        "are",
                        "have",
                        "has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have ……………………… working since morning.",
                    "description": "We make the present perfect continuous tense forms with have been + ing form. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "be",
                        "being",
                        "been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Uncle said that he ………………………. come with me.",
                    "description": "Would is the past tense of will in reported speech.",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "would",
                        "shall"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………………….. visit the beach when I was in Mumbai.",
                    "description": "We use used to to talk about a past habit.",
                    "answers": [
                        "used to",
                        "was used to",
                        "had used to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He …………………………. not go out alone at night.",
                    "description": "When dare is used as a modal auxiliary, it does not the take the marker –s.",
                    "answers": [
                        "dare",
                        "dares"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ……………………………. to speak to me.",
                    "description": "When dare is used as an ordinary verb, it is followed by an infinitive with to. Also, questions and negatives are made with do and does.",
                    "answers": [
                        "doesn't dare",
                        "daren't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You …………………………. write to him.",
                    "description": "When need is used as a modal auxiliary, questions and negatives are made without do and does.",
                    "answers": [
                        "need not",
                        "don't need",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You don’t need ……………………….. for me.",
                    "description": "When need is used as an ordinary verb, it is followed by an infinitive with to.",
                    "answers": [
                        "wait",
                        "to wait",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You …………………………… have told me before borrowing my car.",
                    "description": "We use should to indicate obligation.",
                    "answers": [
                        "should",
                        "would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………………. I carry this bag for you?",
                    "description": "Should is used in polite offers of help.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Should",
                        "Would",
                        "Will"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………………….. you help me with cooking?",
                    "description": "Would is used in polite requests for help.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Would",
                        "Should"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}